(Howard:)What are you thinking,
maybe a big musical number?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm going to make some warm milk
and then turn in.
(Sheldon:)I trust if you two are planning
on engaging in amorous activities...
(Sheldon:)...you'll keep the decibel level
to a minimum.
(Sheldon:)Of course.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
Mm. These are so good. Mm.
(Leonard:)Unbelievable.
(Howard:)-What?
-I was just thinking...
(Leonard:)...we should probably turn in too.
(Penny:)Well, my new bed got delivered.
If you put it together,
you can stay at my place.
Really? That's a lot of work, and it's late.
Yeah, but we won't have to be quiet.
(Howard:)Let's go.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)Sex works even better than chocolate
to modify behavior.
(Sheldon:)I wonder if anyone else
has stumbled onto that.